halomaps.org 2014-12-12

# Halo Custom Edition - Maps, Tags, Tutorials and Assets for t

## Halo Maps Privacy Policy

Halo Maps is an online file repository for the Halo Custom Edition Game. 

**INTRODUCTION**  
Because your privacy is important to us, Halo Maps conducts its business under the following privacy principles: 

**YOUR INFORMATION IS SECURE**  
All the information we compile for your web site and personal information that we collect about you is considered confidential. We have implemented industry standard security mechanisms to protect this information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Examples include limited access, firewalls and security analyzers using SSL encryption to protect transmission of data. 

**USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER DATA COLLECTION METHODS**   
Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make a web site more useful by allowing the site to personalize information for visitors and by storing information about customer preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies. However, you will not be able to access some of the advanced features of the website or be able to login. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION AND EMAIL ADDRESSES**  
**Halo Maps will not sell, share or give out your email address** to any third party for the use of unsolicited email. Halo Maps does reserve the right to perodically contact you via email with offers or announcements about the Halo Maps website. Halo Maps requires registered users who signed up for services, to supply a working e-mail address. This personal information allows Halo Maps to process and fulfill your request for an account. When you submit comments and questions on our products and services via the feedback form on our website we also ask for your e-mail address. This is to allow us to contact you if there are questions about your feedback. We will not sell, share or give out your email address.

Halo Maps may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Halo Maps, our users, or others. 

We will NOT use personally identifiable information about you to: Share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, competitors and other third parties. 

Halo Maps will NOT disclose details about transactions, visitors or customers using this website except to to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Halo Maps, our users, or others. . 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**  
Halo Maps reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this Policy, our Terms of Service Agreement and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with the Service that has been changed.

updated: Aug-06-2009
